A Guide to the Virginia Room Election Files, 1950-2015
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 2003
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 30th, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 31st, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 37th, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 37th - Special Election, 2003
- Virginia State Senate - 39th, 2003
- Vienna, 2003
- Voters' Guides, 2003
- Amendments, 2004
- Bonds - City of Fairfax, 2004
- Bonds - Fairfax County, 2004
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2004
- City of Fairfax - General, 2004
- City of Fairfax - School Board, 2004
- Clifton - Council, 2004
- Clifton - Mayor, 2004
- General - Fall Elections, 2004
- Herndon - Council, 2004
- Herndon - General & Mayor, 2004
- Results - Fall, 2004
- Results - Spring, 2004
- U.S House of Representatives - 10th, 2004
- U.S House of Representatives - 11th, 2004
- U.S House of Representatives -8 th, 2004
- U.S House of Representatives -8th - Primary, 2004
- Vienna - Council, 2004
- Vienna - Mayor, 2004
- Voters' Guides, 2004
- Attorney General, 2005
- Bonds - Schools, 2005
- City of Fairfax, 2005
- General, 2005
- Governor, 2005
- Lieutenant Governor, 2005
- Primaries, 2005
- Primaries - Results, 2005
- Results, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 2005
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2005
- Voters' Guides, 2005
- Amendments, 2006
- Bonds, 2006
- City of Fairfax - Council - May 2006, 2006
- City of Fairfax - Mayor - May 2006, 2006
- City of Fairfax - School Board - May 2006, 2006
- Clifton - May 2006, 2006
- Falls Church, 2006
- General, 2006
- Herndon - May 2006, 2006
- May - General, 2006
- Referendums, 2006
- Results - June, 2006
- Results - May, 2006
- Results -November, 2006
- U.S. Senate, 2006
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 2006
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 2006
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - Primary, 2006
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 2006
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th - Primary, 2006
- Virginia State Senate - 37th - Special Election, 2006
- Vienna - May 2006, 2006
- Voters' Guides, 2006
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Dranesville, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Hunter Mill, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Lee, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Mason, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Providence - Primary, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield - Primary, 2007
- Board of Supervisors - Sully - Primary, 2007
- Bond Referendums, 2007
- Bonds, 2007
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2007
- Clerk of the Court, 2007
- Commonwealth's Attorney, 2007
- General, 2007
- General Assembly, 2007
- Primaries - Results, 2007
- Referendums - School Board, 2007
- Results - November, 2007
- School Board, 2007
- Sheriff, 2007
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th - Primary, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th - Primary, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 2007
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 30th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 31st, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 33rd, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 37th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 39th, 2007
- Virginia State Senate - 39th - Primary, 2007
- Vienna - Council, 2007
- Voters' Guides, 2007
- Bonds, 2008
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2008
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 2008
- City of Fairfax - School Board, 2008
- Clifton - Council, 2008
- Clifton - Mayor, 2008
- General, 2008
- Herndon - Council, 2008
- Herndon - Mayor, 2008
- Results - June, 2008
- Results - May, 2008
- Results - November, 2008
- U.S. Senate, 2008
- U.S. Senate - Primary, 2008
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 2008
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th - Primary, 2008
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 2008
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - Primary, 2008
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 2008
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th - Primary, 2008
- Vienna - Council, 2008
- Vienna - Mayor, 2008
- Voters' Guides, 2008
- Attorney General, 2009
- Attorney General - Republican Convention, 2009
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock - Special Election, 2009
- Board of Supervisors - Braddock - Special Election-Primary, 2009
- Board of Supervisors - Chairman - Special Election, 2009
- Bonds, 2009
- City of Fairfax - Commissioner of the Revenue, 2009
- General, 2009
- Governor, 2009
- Governor - Democratic Primary, 2009
- Lieutenant Governor, 2009
- Lieutenant Governor - Democratic Primary, 2009
- Lieutenant Governor - Republican Convention, 2009
- Results - Fall, 2009
- Results - Spring/Summer, 2009
- Results - Winter, 2009
- School Board - Providence, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th - Primary, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th- Primary, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th - Special Election, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 2009
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2009
- Vienna - Council, 2009
- Voters' Guides, 2009
- Amendments - Constitutional, 2010
- Bond Referendum, 2010
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2010
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 2010
- City of Fairfax - School Board, 2010
- Clifton - Council, 2010
- Clifton - Mayor, 2010
- General, 2010
- Herndon - Council, 2010
- Herndon - Mayor, 2010
- Results, 2010
- School Board - Mason - Special Election, 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th - Primary, 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - Primary (folder 1 of 2), 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - Primary (folder 2 of 2), 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 2010
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th - Primary, 2010
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st - Special Election (3/2/10), 2010
- Virginia State Senate - 37th - Special Election, 2010
- Virginia State Senate - 37th - Special Election Primary, 2010
- Vienna - Council, 2010
- Vienna - Mayor, 2010
- Voters' Guides, 2010
- Braddock District, 2011
- Braddock District - Democratic Primary, 2011
- Chairman, 2011
- Dranesville District, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Hunter Mill, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Lee District, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Mason District, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Mount Vernon District, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Providence District, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Springfield District, 2011
- Board of Supervisors - Sully District, 2011
- Bond Referendum, 2011
- Commonwealth's Attorney, 2011
- General, 2011
- Results - August, 2011
- Results - November, 2011
- School Board, 2011
- School Board - At Large, 2011
- School Board - Braddock, 2011
- School Board - Dranesville District, 2011
- School Board - Hunter Mill, 2011
- School Board - Lee District, 2011
- School Board - Mason District, 2011
- School Board - Mount Vernon District, 2011
- School Board - Providence District, 2011
- School Board - Springfield District, 2011
- School Board - Sully District, 2011
- Sheriff, 2011
- Sheriff - Republican Primary, 2011
- Soil and Water Conservation District, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 48th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th - Democratic Party, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 2011
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 30th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 30th - Democratic Party, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 31st, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 31st - Democratic Party, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 32nd, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 33rd, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 34th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 35th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 36th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 36th - Republican Party, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 37th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 37th - Republican Party, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 39th, 2011
- Virginia State Senate - 39th - Republican Primary, 2011
- Vienna - Council, 2011
- Voters' Guides, 2011
- Bonds, Refendums and Amendments, 2012
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2012
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 2012
- City of Fairfax - School Board, 2012
- Clifton - Council, 2012
- Clifton - Mayor, 2012
- General, 2012
- Council, 2012
- Herndon - Mayor, 2012
- Results - Fall, 2012
- Results - Spring/Summer, 2012
- U.S. Senate, 2012
- U.S. Senate - Republican Primary, 2012
- U.S. House of Representatives - 10th, 2012
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th, 2012
- U.S. House of Representatives - 11th - Republican Primary, 2012
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th, 2012
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th - Democratic Primary, 2012
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th - Special Election (9/4/2012), 2012
- Vienna - Council, 2012
- Vienna - Mayor, 2012
- Voters' Guides - Fall, 2012
- Voters' Guides - Spring/Summer, 2012
- Attorney General, 2013
- Attorney General - Democratic Primary, 2013
- Bonds, Referendums and Amendments, 2013
- City of Fairfax - Commissioner of the Revenue, 2013
- City of Fairfax - Treasurer, 2013
- General, 2013
- Governor, 2013
- Governor - Democratic Primary, 2013
- Governor - Republican Primary, 2013
- Lieutenant Governor, 2013
- Lieutenant Governor - Democratic Primary, 2013
- Lieutenant Governor - Republican State Convention, 2013
- Results, 2013
- Sheriff - Special Election, 2013
- Sheriff - Special Election - Democratic Party, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 35th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 36th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 37th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 38th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 39th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 40th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 41st, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 42nd, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 43rd, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 44th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 45th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 46th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 48th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 49th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 53rd, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 67th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th, 2013
- Virginia House of Delegates - 86th - Democratic Primary, 2013
- Vienna - Council, 2013
- Voters' Guides, 2013
- City of Fairfax - Council, 2014
- City of Fairfax - Mayor, 2014
- City of Fairfax, 2014
- U.S. House of Representatives - 8th District, 2014
- Virginia House of Delegates - 34th - Special Election (1/6/2015), 2015